

Don-Alex Antoine

antoinealex1234@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL O SUMMARY

Bilingual (English/Haitian Creole) Software Engineer with experience in code deployment and environment maintenance. Experience teaching and consulting on best practice tech solutions to a variety of consumers. Creative, organized, versatile, independent worker who is team oriented and solution focused. Adept at HTML, CSS, JavaScript, backend technologies and frameworks.

EDUCATION O

MBA | Business Administration and Management

05/2021

Curry College, Milton MA

Bachelor of Science | Software Development **Curry College, Milton MA**

05/2020

SKILLS O

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Mongoose
- Node.js
- **Express**

MongoDB

- Git
- GitHub
- Heroku
- **Object Oriented Programming** Principles

WORK HISTORY

TEACHING ASSISTANT

09/2017 to 05/2020

Curry College | Milton, MA

- TA for Object Oriented and Structured Programming classes.
- Assisted students in understanding the fundamentals of programming.
- Aided in analyzing problems and guided students towards possible solutions.
- Helped solidify students' knowledge of various programming concepts.
- Assisted in Capstone projects and code reviews.
- Tutored and mentored students in groups of up to 20.
- Created a dynamic and pleasant educational environment conducive to an array of learning styles.
- Implemented practice exercises, code examples and multimedia tutorials enabling students to grasp new concepts quickly.

STUDENT AND STAFF TECHNICAL CONSULTANT

01/2016 to 05/2020

Technology Center, Curry College | Milton, MA

Consulted with students and faculty in need of assistance with campus technology by analyzing symptoms and determining the best possible solutions.

- Installed, supervised, and maintained all computers in 6 different laboratories throughout campus.
- Managed Help Desk tickets in an efficient manner.
- Interacted with customers professionally by phone, email and in-person providing pertinent information and optimal solutions for technical problems.

DIRECTOR OF MEDIA MINISTRY

04/2015 to 08/2020

Abundant Life Church | Cambridge, MA

- Managed technical equipment including the microphone, speakers, soundboard, display screens, etc.
- Rendered and digitized audio from Sunday sermons and uploaded them to the Church's website.
- Managed a volunteer staff of 7 and scheduled volunteers for Sunday services.
- Identified and recruited potential volunteers.
- Worked flexible hours; nights, weekends, and holiday shifts.

ORDER FULFILLMENT SPECIALIST

06/2016 to 07/2018

Home Depot | Watertown, MA

- Provided customer service to patrons in the store and over the phone.
- Performed personal deliveries to clients and contractors.
- Created custom job orders and fulfilled customers' online orders.
- Prepared orders accurately by processing requests, pulling materials from the warehouse, packing boxes, and prepared shipments.

VOLUNTEER WORK O

- Boston Code Camp
- Boston Youth Sanctuary
- Biased Incident Response Team (BIRT)
- Digital Literacy Committee

AFFILIATIONS O

- Member of the Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers (IEEE)
- Member of the Association for Computing Machinery (ACM)
- Treasurer of the ACM and IEEE Curry College chapter
- Treasurer of Tech Club, Curry College